RIAJUL ISLAM

Address : Road No. 1, West Nandipara, Khilgaon, Dhaka 1219

Phone :+8801722787007

E-mail : riajul.islam.dev@gmail.com



GitHub:

www.github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/riajul-islam-dev

Skype:

join.skype.com/invite/y4awZfHii9yl

Website:

https://riajul-islam-dev.github.io

Skill Highlights

Front-end Technologies:

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax
- Vue.js

Back-end Technologies:

- C, C++, Golang
- PHP, MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Laravel, Yii Framework
- ASP.NET Core MVC

Additional Skills:

Internet of Things (IoT)

References

Dr. Md. Nawab Yousuf Ali

Professor, Department of Computer

Science and Engineering

East West University

Email: nawab@ewubd.edu

Tel: +88 09666775577 Ext. 104

Dr. Ahmed Wasif Reza

Professor, Department of Computer

Science and Engineering

East West University

Email: wasif@ewubd.edu

Tel: +88 09666775577 Ext. 394

Web App ASP.NET Core MVC

ASP.NET Core MVC based Web App to purchase

products

Git: https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/WebApp ASP.NET Core MVC

IOT Based Project

IOT Based Smart Window with Remote Controlling System

Git: https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/IOT-Based-Smart-Window-with-Remote-Controlling-System

Career Objective

Experienced Full Stack Web Developer with a proven track record of solution-focused work and an unwavering commitment to web development. Known for my self-motivation, team-building skills, and consistently delivering best results in this ever-evolving field.

Education

Japanese-language proficiency Level N3

VENTURAS Ltd., Dhaka (May 15, 2022 - Nov 30, 2022)

BSc, in Computer Science & Engineering

East West University, Dhaka (May 2014 – August 2019)

HSC in Science (Jul 2011 – Jun 2013)

Advanced Residential Model College, Mymensingh

SSC in Science (Jan 2003 – Mar 2011)

Agricultural University High School, Mymensingh

Experience

Intern Web Developer

December 2022 – February 2023

ZUU Co.,Ltd., Japan

Full Stack Web Developer

October 2021 – April 2022

NexKraft Limited, Dhaka

Full Stack Web Developer

May 2022 - To date Leotech BD, Dhaka

Associate Web Developer

September 2020 - October 2021

Perky Rabbit, Dhaka

Projects

CaseHub (BRAC's Legal & Compliance Website)

Developed this Website's Phase 3

Link: https://casehub.brac.net

Legal Information Management System

Case & Lawyer Management System for any Organization Git: https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/lims-skote-laravel-

starterkit

Online Shop Yii

Online Ecommerce Shop in Yii Framework

Git: https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/Online Shop Yii

Ecommerce in Laravel

Ecommerce Management System for any Brand or Company with POS, stock, Employee & Customer management.

Git: https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-Dev/Arong-Dhong

Academic System in Raw PHP

Management system for Admin, Teacher, Student & Staff's Profile, Exam & Result system

Git: https://github.com/Riajul-Islam-

Dev/PerkyRabbit__Result_Publishment_System